{
  "trueFalseQuestions": [
    {
      "question": "A triangle has five sides.",
      "answer": "false",
      "options": "Remember that a triangle has three sides, not five."
    },
    {
      "question": "A normal adult mouth contains 32 teeth, including the wisdom teeth.",
      "answer": "false",
      "options": "It is 32 teeth EXCLUDING the wisdom teeth."
    },
    {
      "question": "The Sun is a star.",
      "answer": "true",
      "options": "Remember, the sun is indeed a star."
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 8 = 64",
      "answer": "true",
      "options": "8 x 8 is like doing 8 + 8 + 8 + 8 + 8 + 8 + 8 + 8. This will givce you 64."
    },
    {
      "question": "John Adams was the first US President.",
      "answer": "false",
      "options": "SECOND President."
    }
  ],
    "textInputQuestions" : [
      {
        "question": "3 x 4 = ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "answerTextFieldId": "4 + 4 = 8, 8 + 4 = 12."
      },
      {
        "question": "Fill in the blank: Today, I walked my ___ to the park.",
        "answer": "dog",
        "answerTextFieldId": "People tend to walk their dogs at the park."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many sides does a square have?",
        "answer": "4",
        "answerTextFieldId": "A square has 4 sides."
      },
      {
        "question": "What state of matter is water usually in?",
        "answer": "liquid",
        "answerTextFieldId": "Water is usually in its liquid state."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is handing in work late worth doing?",
        "answer": "no",
        "answerTextFieldId": "Self-explanatory."
      }
    ]

}
